1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. custom.BrowserHelper.closeFirefoxPopup()
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
21. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
25. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
29. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
37. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
41. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"))
45. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
49. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
61. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 7)
65. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
69. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
73. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
77. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Online Payment - Cradit Card"))
81. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Checkbox__I accept"))
85. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Checkout_Payment"))
89. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/iframe_Credit Card"), 10)
93. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/iframe_Credit Card"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
97. delay(10)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/field_cardNumber"), "5156 8399 3770 6777")
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/field_cardExp"), "01/30")
109. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/field_cvv2"), "993")
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/btn-closed-pay"))
117. waitForAlert(10)
121. alertText = getAlertText()
125. comment(alertText)
129. acceptAlert()
133. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"), 7)
137. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"))
141. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/sp-order-list-item"))
145. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/btn-cencel"), 10)
149. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/btn-cencel"))
153. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/button_OK"), 7)
157. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/button_OK"))
161. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/Message_Success"), 10)
165. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/Message_Success"))
169. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/text_order_status"), 5)
173. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/text_order_status"), "CANCEL")
177. takeScreenshot()
181. closeBrowser()